paleoburn.com 2013-11-16

# Privacy Policy - PaleoBurn

## Effective Date:  04/08/2013

This privacy policy applies to http://paleoburn.com/ owned and operated by Primal Health, LP (“Primal Health”, “We”, “Us”, and” Ours”).   This privacy policy describes how Primal Health collects and uses the personal information you provide on http://paleoburn.com/.  It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. This privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  By using our site, you consent to our[ privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

Primal Health, LP has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe’s program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy_seals_and_services/consumer_privacy/privacy-programs-requirements.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information.  The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, http://paleoburn.com/ and does not cover information that may be collected offline or through 3rd party business affiliates.

TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy Trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [Support@PaleoBurn.com](mailto:Support@PaleoBurn.com).  If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://watchdog.truste.com/pvr.php?page=complaint)

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order, enter a contest, use our member health tracking tools or subscribe to our newsletter.  Any data we request that is not required will be specified as voluntary or optional.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, billing address and credit card information.  For health evaluation purposes, we may also collect your gender and date of birth. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

We also display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements.  With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name.  If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [Support@PaleoBurn.com](mailto:Support@PaleoBurn.com)  .

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To create and administer your account;

(your information is used to create an account profile enabling you to use our service).

To personalize your experience

(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

To improve our website

(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

To improve customer service

(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

To process transactions

(We use a payment processor to facilitate transaction between users of the site and process billing information)

To send periodic emails

(The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order or request, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, promotions, related product or service information, etc.)

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

How do we protect your information?

The security of your personal information is important to us. We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request or place an order.

These security measures include: password protected directories and databases to safeguard your information or PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.  After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [Support@PaleoBurn.com](mailto:Support@PaleoBurn.com).

Do we use cookies and other tracking technologies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process your questions and related information, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.  We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

We partner with third party ad networks to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites.  Our ad network partners uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.  If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking [Here](http://preferences.truste.com/).  Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising.  You will continue to receive generic ads.

We may employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.  The information gathered by clear gifs is never tied to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

The use of tracking technologies by our service providers, technology partners or other 3rd party assets on the site is not covered by our privacy policy.  These 3rd parties may use cookies, clear gifs, images, and scripts to help them better manage their content on our site.   We do not have access or control over these technologies.  We do not tie the information gathered to our Customers’ or Users’ personally identifiable information.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties.  We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing your payments or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us, and are contractually obligated to keep your information confidential.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, such as a subpoena, or similar legal process; when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to enforce our site policies, investigate fraud or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

If Primal Health is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets,  you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,

User Access and Choice

If your personally information changes, you may correct, update, amend, remove or ask to have it removed by making the change on your user account settings page, by emailing our Customer Support at [Support@PaleoBurn.com](mailto:Support@PaleoBurn.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.  If you no longer desire our service, you may delete your account by contacting us at [Support@PaleoBurn.com](mailto:Support@PaleoBurn.com).  We will respond to your request within 30 days.

Be advised, we will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Opting-Out

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you, as well as other periodic emails of both promotional and transactional nature.  Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter and/or other promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [Support@PaleoBurn.com](mailto:Support@PaleoBurn.com).

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.  As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

Our Blog

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.  Anytime you post on our blog please be aware that you are posting using a third party application and we have no access or control over this information.

To request removal of your personal information from our blog, you can both log into the third party application and remove your comment or you can contact the appropriate third party application. Your interaction with these features is governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

Contests

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests on our site.  If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you.  Participation in these contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information.  The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as age and gender and personal photos).

We use this information to notify contest winners, award prizes and post success stories.  If you don’t wish to have your personal information published if you win, please refrain from entering the contest.

Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products,services or provide links to 3rd party sites on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies that differ from Primal Health.  If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.  We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

Social Media Widgets / Links

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button, and links to our Facebook and Twitter Pages.  These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  If we find that we have inadvertently collected information from someone under 13 years of age, we will delete the information immediately.

CAN-SPAM Compliance

We have taken the necessary steps to ensure that we are compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003 by never sending out misleading information.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

paleoburn.com/support

341 N. Central Expressway Suite 341

McKinney, TX 75070

[Support@PaleoBurn.com](mailto:Support@PaleoBurn.com).877-300-7849

Privacy Policy Customer Pledge

We pledge to you, our customer, that we have made a dedicated effort to bring our privacy policy in line with the the following important privacy laws and initiatives:

  * Federal Trade Commission Fair

  * California Online Privacy Protection Act

  * Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

  * Privacy Alliance

  * Controlling the Assault of Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act

If at any time you have a cause that needs to be disputed please fill out the [Trust Guard Dispute Resolution form](http://secure.trust-guard.com/disputesystem/).

Respectfully,  
Ken Burge  
PaleoBurn.com
